<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Anton Lee</title><link>https://antonjameslee.com/</link><description>Recent content on Anton Lee</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>All rights reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 11:40:18 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antonjameslee.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating the game of Gothello</title><link>https://antonjameslee.com/posts/gothelloconcept/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 11:40:18 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://antonjameslee.com/posts/gothelloconcept/</guid><description>What if Othello and Go were mixed? They share lots of similarities so it must be possible right? As part of the Smoke and Mirrors paper at the University of Waikato, me and one other student created a mashup strategy game combining the game of Othello and Go. Our end product was a web application and was playable online. I worked on the Java server and a ReactJS client while my teammate worked on coding the rules.</description></item><item><title>The D-BUS or the secret social network for programs</title><link>https://antonjameslee.com/posts/dbus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:33:14 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://antonjameslee.com/posts/dbus/</guid><description>Programs on your computer have a secret way of talking to each other called the D-Bus. They know to pause music when you get a call. Your spreadsheet talks to your word processor. Chrome knows how to open your native save file dialog. How are our programs talking to each other and why were you not invited?
The D-Bus is this mystic forum where applications yell at each other to do things or simply yell about what they are doing.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://antonjameslee.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 12:52:44 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://antonjameslee.com/about/</guid><description>Anton Lee Currently studying computer science and data analytics at the university of Waikato
A mostly self-taught (working on my formal education at the moment) programmer with real-world experience. I’m the sort of person that codes for fun and as work. I aspire to contribute positively to truly important and valuable projects. I&amp;rsquo;m hardworking, good at communication, and well organized. I always strive to learn new things and challenge myself to be better and better.</description></item><item><title>Programming Scholarship Report</title><link>https://antonjameslee.com/projects/theasthai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:17:46 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://antonjameslee.com/projects/theasthai/</guid><description>figcaption{ text-align: center; padding: 5px; font-size: 10px; color: grey; font-style: oblique; } img{ cursor: pointer; } Please keep it in mind that this document was aimed at NCEA technology markers. As such, it uses a lot of design terminology and is a bit shy when it comes to technical jargon. It&amp;rsquo;s also excessively long.
TL;DR I make a website to let people make events and order tickets to those events</description></item><item><title>Blue</title><link>https://antonjameslee.com/projects/blue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 16:17:46 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://antonjameslee.com/projects/blue/</guid><description>Blue was a game me and a friend made for NCEA Level 2 programming. The game was a short stealth game where you played as a ball of light running away from dementor like creatures. It was our first unity project and as such lacks a lot of polish and is a little buggy. I think the mood and the ambiance are the aspects that turned out best in the game.</description></item><item><title>Mad</title><link>https://antonjameslee.com/projects/mad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 14:14:38 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://antonjameslee.com/projects/mad/</guid><description>Mad was one of my earliest large projects. It was coded in C# using windows forms which led to interesting challenges to get the graphics I wanted. All of the graphics were created by me. I used illustrator for the Icons, Photoshop for the map and Blender for the rockets and explosions.
The given brief was to create an educational game. I decided I would educate people about mutually assured destruction.</description></item></channel></rss>